Finding aid for the Paul Monette papers, 1945-1995 LSC.1707
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Biographical
  - Subseries 2.3: Relationships
    - Travel: Winston Wilde/Russia and Scandinavia: Cruise tickets, travel documents for WW, bill for medication from ship's doctor for PM, mementos of ship., August 1994.; In leather zippered portfolio. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Travel: Vancouver, Rome: Items from Windsor Travel., 1993, 1994. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Correspondences, Winston Wilde about Monette's Writings, 1996-1997 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2.4: Press, Appearances, and Honors
    - Appearances: Sermon: North Parish Church of Andover Unitarian Universalist: Program., February 8, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Includes short biography.
    - Appearances: Radio: WBUR: Sound Recording, April 30, 1978.; 1 audio cassette. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Appearances: Sound Recording: Randy Alfred, The Gay Life., April 19, 1981.; 1 audio cassette. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Press: Article / interview by Craig Rowland: Re: Lightfall: In: New York Native., December 19, 1983 / January 1, 1984.; p.31. (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Article mentions most writings up to the date of Lightfall, including novelizations of screenplays. This description also under material for Lightfall.
    - Honors: City of West Hollywood Certificate of Commendation: Signed by Babette Lang, mayor, etc., November 29, 1984.; 1 leaf. In folder. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Press, "Taking Care of Mrs. Carroll" and "Borrowed Time", 1979-1988 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Appearances: Video Recording: Lifestyle Update: Show no. 68. Christmas gala special., 1988.; 1 video cassette. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Appearances: Sound Recording: LATC., December 1988.; 1 audio cassette. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Appearances: Speech and Newsletter Announcement: Los Angeles Gay & Lesbian Community Service Center, November 4, 1988.; 2 leaves photocopy and 2 leaves typscript. With handwritten notations by PM. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Appearances/Press: Correspondence Received: The Survivors: People Living With Aids: (letter). (event)., January 25, 1989 February 3, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      From talent coordinator confirming PM's participation and press release.
    - Press, "Afterlife", 1990 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Appearances: Sound Recording: Michael Jackson (KABC Radio): With Paul Monette, Torie Osborne, Bill Capobianco., January 29, 1990.; 1 audio cassette. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Appearances: Video Recording: Geraldo, March 17, 1990.; 1 video cassette. (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Hour-long discussion with Larry Kramer, etc. Aired April 19, 1990.
    - Appearances: Video Recording: Geraldo: Letters Received After Appearance, April 23 and 29, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Also letter April 20 from Larry Grusin.
    - Appearances: UCLA: The Claiming of World Citizenship: Gay and Lesbian Literature Explodes into the Nineties: Organizational Material: Schedule., April 21, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 21)
      PM in panel, The Revolutionary Literature of AIDS. Includes short biographies of participants (Michael Denneny, Michael Nava, Pat Califia, etc).
    - Press/Publicity: Newsletter Article with photograph of PM: Valley Business Alliance, May 1990. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Press: Clipping: Vanity Fair: Night table reading, May 1990. (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Quote from PM about what he reads at night.
    - Appearances: Correspondences Received: UCLA: Flowering of Gay and Lesbian Literature: From Bob Manners., November 21, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Manners was a student / attendee. Praising the class taught by PM and Elisabeth Nonas.
    - Press: Article on PM's Speech: CSU (Colorado State University?), October 4, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 26)
      On PM speech.
    - Press: Andover Bulletin (Alumni Magazine): Correspondences Received: Original interview request letter from Nancy Boutilier., 1991. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Press: Andover Bulletin (Alumni Magazine): Interviewed by Nancy Boutilier. Respondents., 1991. (Box 4, Folder 28)
      SEE ALSO: Fan mail from Phillips Academy students.
    - Appearances: Correspondences Received: Outwrite '92: From David Feinberg., February 11, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: State University of New York Oswego: Doctor of Letters: Correspondences: Address., May 16, 1992.; [2] leaves. Typescript (photocopy). 2 copies. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: State University of New York Oswego: Doctor of Letters: Program: 131st Commencement class of 1992., May 16, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: State University of New York Oswego: Doctor of Letters: Correspondence: Thanks from Coy D. Ludwig., May 21, 1992.; 2 leaves. Typed, signed. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: State University of New York Oswego: Doctor of Letters: Clippings, June 1992 and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Press: Correspondence Received: Los Angeles Times: Charles Salmore., Typed, signed. (Box 4, Folder 36)
      Possibly written after article which appeared Summer 1992 (?), or perhaps refers to a review of Borrowed Time(?).
    - Appearances: Transcript of filmed interview., August 8, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Honors: Correspondence Received: Pen Freedom to Write Award, August 4, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Honors: Program: Pen Freedom to Write Award, October 4, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Honors/Press: Pen Freedom to Write Award: Keeping Society Honest, an Interview with Paul Monette by David L. Ulin: In: Center, the magazine of PEN Center USA West., Winter 1993.; pp.10-11, 23. (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Press/Recording: Love Alone: 18 Elegies for Rog: Performance of Jeffrey Brody settings., June 16, 1992.; Cassette recording. (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Introduction, Here, Gardenias, etc.,
      See other material in Box 17.
    - Honors: Memorabilia: Pen Freedom to Write Award: City of Los Angeles congratulations signed by Michael K. Woo, councilman 13th district., October 4, 1992.; 1 leaf in folder. (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Congratulations Paul Monette upon being honored by PEN West for promoting literary freedom throughout the world.
    - Appearances: U.S. Holocaust Museum: Photograph in: United States Holocaust Memorial Museum Newsletter., Spring 1993. (Box 36, Folder 16)
      Prints photograph of PM and WW, with quotation from PM.
    - Correspondences, Monette's form response to well wishers after receiving National Book Award (Descriptive note by WW: "I had Paul make these up c. 1993 (post-NBA) to deal w / the deluge."), circa 1993 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Press: Article: UCLA Event: Paul Monette Speaks of Joy of Being Free, Eloquent Truth Telling, His Dog Puck, by Dan Luckenbill: In: The UCLA Lesbian and Gay Faculty / Staff Network Newsletter vol.4 no.3., Spring 1993.; p.5. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: Wesleyan University: Doctor of Letters: Nomination: Correspondences from David Schorr., November 1992.; 3 leaves. Typed, signed. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Refers to his putting PM's name forward for honorary degree.
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: Wesleyan University: Doctor of Letters: Invitation and Arrangements: Correspondences from William Chace., November 30 and December 8, 1992; May 11, 1993.; Each letter is 1 leaf. Typed, signed. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Also printed invitations and schedule.
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: Wesleyan University: Doctor of Letters: Program: One hundred and sixty-first commencement., May 30, 1993.; 2 copies. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: Wesleyan University: Doctor of Letters: Publicity and Memorabilia: Cover letter for degree, article, placecards., May 30, 1993 and Summer 1993. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Placecards for: PM, David Schorr, Winston Wilde.
    - Honors: Honorary Degrees: Wesleyan University: Doctor of Letters: Photographs: Unidentified. (?)., May 30, 1993; 2 color enlargements. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Appearances: Correspondence Received: UCLA Event: Peter Thorslev, etc. (?)., 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Enclosed PT's introduction for the first scheduled talk at UCLA. PM unable to appear that date. Cf. next file. Letter from Barbara Packer February 9, 1993.
    - Appearances: Fliers and Correspondence Received: UCLA Event: From: Daniel G. Calder, Dan Luckenbill, Peter Thorslev., February 18, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Appearances: Program: GLAAD Los Angeles Media Awards: 4th Annual: Out and In Focus., March 20, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 10)
      PM presented SF Kolzak award to Sir Ian McKellen.
    - Appearances: Correspondences: GLAAD Los Angeles Media Awards: 4th Annual: from Ian McKellen., March 21 and May 14, 1993.; 2 leaves. Holograph, signed. (Box 5, Folder 11)
      First is card with envelope, referring to the GLAAD ceremony.
    - Press: Work Used in an Academic Project: Used in Master's degree thesis by David Barrett., April 7, 1993 (after). (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Press: Work Used in an Academic Project: Correspondence Received: Invitation to David Barrett's graduation ceremony with his note., April 29, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Appearances: Flier: One Institute 35th Annual Lecture Series, October 3, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Appearances: Correspondence Received: One Institute 35th Annual Lecture Series: from Walter L. Williams and Toby Johnson., October 1993.; Each is 1 leaf. Typed, signed. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Appearances: Printed program and schedule: Time Warner Executive Forum: Coming Out: Gay Issues in America, November 8, 1993.; Schedule has holograph notes by PM. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Appearances: Correspondences Received: Time Warner Executive Forum: Coming Out: Gay Issues in America (Box 5, Folder 22)
      From: Nan C. DuBois, Rich Mayora, David Munk.
    - Honors: Program: Lifetime Achievement Awards, December 1, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Presented in gratitude by Richard J. Riordan, mayor, Ferd Eggan, City AIDS Coordinator.
    - Press: Article: Pen Center West Awards: In: PEN Center West newsletter., Winter 1994.; Clipping, pp.10-11. (Box 5, Folder 24)
      PM accepted award for David Geffen, December 1993.
    - Honors: Correspondence Received: Chuck Rowland Award, March 3, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Received from Christopher Street West / Los Angeles.
    - Appearances: Program: Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research: Stonewall 25: A Quarter Century of Lesbian and Gay Liberation and its Origins in Southern California: Annual Awards Dinner, March 12, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 26)
      PM a keynote speaker.
    - Appearances: Correspondences Received and Reporting: Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research: Stonewall 25: A Quarter Century of Lesbian and Gay Liberation and its Origins in Southern California: Annual Awards Dinner: Letter from Steven Saylor, enclosing clipping. (?)., April 3, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      1 leaf. Typed, signed S. Date on letter: March 24, 1994.
    - Honors: Honorary Degree: Invitation and Processional Instructions: City University of New York: Doctor of Letters: Correspondence from Theresa Passantino and printed invitation., April 1, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Honors: Honorary Degree: Program: City University of New York: Doctor of Letters, May 26, 1994.; 2 copies. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Appearances: Flier: A Different Light: Hosts a very special evening with Paul Monette. [From DL]., August 14, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Appearances: Invitations and Programs: GLAAD/Los Angeles: A Celebration of Paul Monette, October 1, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Appearances: GLAAD/Los Angeles: A Celebration of Paul Monette: As Vulcan Falls from Heaven (for Paul Monette), by Terry Wolverton., 1994.; 2 leaves. Typescript. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Appearances: Articles: GLAAD/Los Angeles: A Celebration of Paul Monette, October 1994.; 2 clippings. (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Appearances: Correspondences Received: St. Thomas the Apostle Church: from Otis Charles enclosing Karen Ocamb's B.A.R. article. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Appearances: Loyola University, Chicago: Full show of Paul Monette., December 11, 1994.; Cassette recording. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Appearances: Correspondences Received: Various Schools, Organizations, Events: Requesting PM to speak., 1988-1994. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Press: Correspondences Received: Request for interviews with PM., 1988-1994. (Box 8, Folder 1)
      An extensive file. Some enclose copies or photocopies of articles using interviews, transcripts of interviews, etc. Includes note from Rudy Kikel, among many others.
    - Appearances/Press: Correspondences, 1988-1994. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press: Correspondences Received Requesting Use of PM's Work: Counseling, Sermons, Teaching, etc., 1988-1995. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Press: Winning the War: By Bohdan Zachary: In: The Advocate. no.677., March 21, 1995.; pp.59-60, [62-63]. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Press: Nonfiction: Brief Interviews: PM quoted. (Box 49, Folder 15)
      Includes quotations about Nureyev and AIDS, etc.
    - Press: Nonfiction: Brief Information: Details about PM and his writings and beliefs. (Box 49, Folder 16)
      Clippings.
    - Press/Recording: West of Yesterday, East of Summer: New and Selected Poems / Dr. Burnout, To GB from Tuscany: Musical adaptions, composer / performer not identified., Cassette recording. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Press, "Brink of Summer's End", 1997 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Press and Obituaries, Magazines, 1992-1997 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Press and Obituaries, Newspapers and Fliers, 1992-2003 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Interview, Posthumous, "In Los Angeles" Magazine, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Cassette tapes and videotapes: including various interviews, AIDS-related television and radio programs, and recorded messages from friends., 1980s to mid-1990s (Box 38, Box 39)
      A few of the notable items in these boxes have been referenced individually in the finding aid, such as the recording of Monette's Geraldo appearance.
  - Subseries 2.5: Projects, Involvements, etc.
    - Correspondences: The Names Project: Letter from David Gere, October 21, 1988. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Thanking PM for being a reader at the Quilt in Washington, D.C.
    - Correspondences Sent: From Paul Monette on ACT UP letterhead., June 1989.; Photocopy (?). (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Signature in blue. Addressed: Dear Friend. Begins: As I write today, the AIDS nightmare enters its second decade.
    - Sale: Photographs: Inventory by Nancy Escher., December 19, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Sale: Photographs: Invitation to January Kesner Gallery., 1993. (Box 4, Folder 14)
      All proceeds ... will benefit the Monette / Horwitz Trust, a foundation whose purpose is to suport research in Gay and Lesbian Scholarship.
    - Correspondences: Donations: City of Angels Hospice Foundation, May and July 1990. (Box 4, Folder 22)
      re use of Don Bachardy portrait of PM for fundraising. Request and formal agreement letters. [No material from DB].
    - Correspondences Received: Soliciting papers: Paul Monette Papers, August 28, 1992 and January 28, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Sherry Thomas (San Francisco Public Library), Lisa Browar (New York Public Library).
    - Article: Paul Monette Papers: In: The UCLA Lesbian and Gay Faculty / Staff Network Newsletter. vol.4 no.3., Spring 1993.; p.4. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      See also: UCLA Librarian article, filed in Box 22 folder 10.
    - Correspondences Received: Monette/Horwitz Trust: From people who want to make donations., 1993-1994. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Memorabilia: March on Washington: Program and place cards from dinner., Spring 1993.; Pamphlet and 2 cards. (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Paul and The Speaker (Speaker of the House Tom Foley).
    - Correspondence Received: UCLA AIDS Institute: From Irvin Chen, Rhona McNally., July and September 1993. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondences Received: AIDS Related Organizations: Requests for PM to support projects., 1990-1993. (Box 8, Folder 10)
      re Paul Reed's books, the Q Journal, conversation with Guru Ma Jaya, Jonathan Vipond, Momentum Broadway Cares, etc.
    - Correspondences Received: AIDS Related Organizations: Letters of Thanks for Support, 1990, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondences Received: Gay & Lesbian Studies, 1992-1993. (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Various topics: research, scholarship, teaching, etc.
    - Correspondences Received: Requests and acknowledgement of support., 1992-1994. (Box 8, Folder 14)
      PM did not make donations to all organizations so requesting.
    - Correspondences Received: Gay & Lesbian Writers: From young writers, seeking advice., 1993-1994, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondences Received: Gay & Lesbian Organizations: Lesbian and Gay Historical Society [San Diego]., 1993. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Correspondences Received: Gay & Lesbian Organizations: From Jim Marks, Lambda Literary Awards., 1994.; 1 leaf. Typed, signed. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Portrait of Pope John Paul II. (Box 51, Folder 12)
      PM's note: Souvenir of Honey and Victor's visit to Akron April 25, 1994 [PM had earlier torn up a picture of the Pope in public].
    - Notes, Unidentified, Undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.6: Personal Materials
    - Birth certificate: Paul Landry Monette., October 16, 1945.; 1 leaf. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Lawrence General Hospital [Lawrence, Massachusetts], Beatrice K. Barnes R.N,, hospital administrator and Richard J. Neil M.D., attending physician.
    - Travel Documents, etc.: Passports, 1970s, 1971, 1976.; 2 items. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      1971 bears no stamps, 1976 bears stamps from France (1976, 1980) and England (1977).
    - Contracts and Invoices, Wendy Weil, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Contracts, Paramount, "One Good Reason", 1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Contracts, CBS, "No Secrets", 1984 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Contracts, Just Green, "Secret of the Catacombs", 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Contracts, Embassy, "Street Smarts" and "15 Minutes", 1982-1984 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Contracts, Francois de Menil, "The Hamptons", 1981 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Statements, Cash Management, 1981-1984 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Statements and Receipts, State Savings Visa, 1980-1984 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Contracts, Universal, "Time Out" and "Charade-Type Film", 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Statements, Dreyfus Liquid Assets, 1980-1983 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Statements, State Savings, 1980-1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Contracts, Universal, "Scarface", 1982-1984 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Loan, Inter-Guild Federal Credit Union, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Contracts, Disney, "The Manicurist", 1985 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Contracts, Robert Levithan, "Just the Summers", 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and Receipts, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Expense Reimbursements, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Contracts, Avon, "Final Meeting," "No Witnesses," and "The Long Shot", 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Royalty Statements, Avon, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Contracts, Warner Brothers, "American Maid", 1983-1985 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Contracts, Major Talent and The Artist Agency, 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Royalty Statements, Little, Brown, "Taking Care of Mrs. Carroll", 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Contracts, Resenman/Missel, "Time Out" and "Double Lock", 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Income Taxes, 1979-1985 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Contracts, Avon, "The Gold Diggers", 1978 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Royalty Statements, Avon, "Gold Diggers," "Long Shot," "No Witnesses," and "Nosferatu", 1979-1984 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Contracts, FDM Productions, "Nothing But the Truth", 1981 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Datebooks/Calendars: Schedule of activities for Cesar's visit., December 1978.; 1 holograph leaf. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Datebooks/Calendars: Entries in: Le Book Los Angeles., 1982. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Datebooks/Calendars: Entries in: Le Book Los Angeles., 1984. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Datebooks/Calendars: Entries in: Week at a Glance., 1988. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Contracts., 1980-1989. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - 7 books from Monette's private library: some are annotated by Monette and some are inscribed, such as Packer's "Emerson's Fall" by the author and Baudelaire's "Les Fleurs du Mal" by the translator, Richard Howard: also includes, Stein's "Autobiography of Alice B. Toklas," Murdoch's "The Black Prince," Greene's "A Sort of Life," Dinesen's "Shadows of the Grass," and a Norton Anthology of English Literature., 1960s through 1980s (Box 57)
    - Personal Documents, Travel Visa, Driver's License, Insurance Card, and Tiffany Receipt, early 1990s (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - PM's Health: HIV Infection: Notes on Medications taken., ca. 1990-1993. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - AIDS: Experimental Treatments, 1990-1994. (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Unsolicited information about experimental treatments for AIDS.
    - Datebooks/Calendars: Entries in: Week-at-a-glance., 1992. (Box 4, Folder 29)
      With hand-written appointments with friends and doctors and readings.
    - PM's Health: AIDS: Correspondence received from doctor., September 28, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Travel: Europe: Ephemera: Cocktail napkins, Hotel Hassler Roma., n.d. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Travel: Passport, November 2, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Travel: Luggage Tags: TWA Ambassador's Club with PM's name and address. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Datebooks/Calendars: Entries in: 1994 Weekly. There's Still Time!, [Printed cutout] taped to front. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Royalty Payments: Statements., 1990-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Residual Payments: Receipts., 1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Contracts. Also miscellaneous financial notes., 1990-1993. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Medical Records, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Medical Records, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Medical Records, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Medical Records, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Medical Records, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Medical Records, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Medical Records, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Forest Lawn Paperwork, DNR Form, and Death Certificate, Monette, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2.7: Memorial Items
    - Programs, etc. Also, button with PM photo: Directors Guild Service, February 1995. (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Recording: Benefit: Sharing Our Talents, April 27, 1995.; Video cassette. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Tributes: Paul Monette, by Malcolm Boyd., n.d. [1993?]. (Box 52, Folder 2)
      cf. article in Frontiers, which uses some quotations from this, but this is lengthier.
    - Service Arrangements: Text of WW's speech, seating plan, and other memorial arrangements, including receipts, etc. Also some letters received about details of arrangements. Memorabilia filed previously, extra programs here. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Service, New York: Memorabilia: Programs., n.d. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Condolences Received by WW: Letter from Bill Lockyer, California Senate. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Condolences: WW's list of those phoning with condolences. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Records: Health and memorial information. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Contributions in PM's Memory: Notice of memorial contribution. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Condolences: Correspondences from Sascha Bittner to WW., July 1995. (Box 52, Folder 9)
      With extensive enclosures.
    - Obituaries: Various publications., Clippings and copies of publications. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Contributions in PM's Memory: Letter from Morris Kight, enclosing copy of program with list of contributions in PM's memory to the Southern California Libray. (letter)., April 11, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Names in program: Eric Gordon, Dan Luckenbill, etc.